kkr.in 2016-11-24

# Kolkata Knight Riders - Privacy Policy

This website is the official website of Kolkata Knight Riders which is owned, operated and managed by "Knight Riders Sports Private Limited"

PRIVACY

We respect the privacy of everyone who visits this website and take great care to protect your information. We are committed to maintaining the privacy and security of information of all fans, customers and visitors of this website.

To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our policy on the collection and use of personal and other information and the steps we take to ensure that all such information is kept secure. By entering this website you are consenting to the terms of our privacy policy and to our use of information collected in ways that are compatible with this privacy policy. By submitting your personal information to us, you will be treated as having given your permission for the processing of your personal information as set out in this policy.

INFORMATION COLLECTED

We do not require your personal information for you to obtain access to most of our website.

We collect personal information from visitors on a voluntary basis such as name, company details, title, address, contact numbers, e-mail address, date of birth and other relevant data. We may also obtain such personal information from e-mails and other written and verbal communication with you.

We may supplement the information that you provide with other information that we obtain in our dealings with you or which we receive from our business partners or other entities.

INFORMATION COLLECTED

Personal Information

All personal information that we obtain about you will be recorded, used, and protected by us in accordance with the current data protection legislations and our privacy policy.

We will primarily collect and use your personal information for business purposes in order:

  * to enable you to download product information, order products and make use of certain other features of our website;
  * to provide information or interactive services through this website, to your e-mail address or, where you wish it to be sent by post, to your postal address;
  * to create an individual profile for you so that we can understand your preferences and inform you of our or select third party products, services events or special offers that may be of interest to you;
  * to seek your feedback or to contact you in relation to the services offered on our website;
  * to process orders or applications submitted by you;
  * to administer or otherwise carry out our obligations in relation to any agreement you have with us;
  * to anticipate and resolve problems in respect of any goods or services supplied to you;
  * to create products or services that may meet your needs;
  * to process and respond to requests, improve our operations, and communicate with visitors about our products, services and businesses;
  * to allow you to subscribe to our news letter;
  * to track activity on our website.

We may also remove all the personally identifiable information and use the rest for historical, statistical or scientific purposes.

If you e-mail us or join discussion lists, you are voluntarily releasing information to us. Your e-mail address will be used by us to respond to you.

Disclosure of Information

We may share your personal information (including details of your purchasing preferences) with:

  * Any related companies in the group;
  * select third parties to administer and process your requests, for credit control and debt collection, to maintain our systems or to comply with legal obligations and our business partners, sponsors and advertisers.

Each of these entities may wish to keep you informed of services, products, events and special offers made available by such entity. In all cases, we will take great care to ensure that your personal information is processed in accordance with applicable laws and only for the purposes set out in this policy.

Discontinuation of Communication of Offers

Please note that if you prefer not to be contacted either by us or by any other related companies in the group or other third parties referred to above, you may click the relevant boxes on the screen upon which you provide information or alternatively you may email us.

Please note that if you do opt out of receiving information, we will be unable to keep you informed of any new services, products, events or special offers that may interest you and our ability to inform you of ticketing opportunities may be affected.

If you are concerned about our use and disclosure of your personal information, do contact us.

Non-Personal Information

At this website, information sent by your web browser may be automatically collected. This information typically includes your domain name (the site after the '@' in your e-mail address). It may also contain your user name (the name before the '@' in your e-mail address). Other examples of information collected by our server include the Internet Protocol (“IP”) address used to connect the visitor's computer to the Internet, operating system and platform, the average time spent on our website, pages viewed, information searched for, access times, websites visited before and after a visitor visits our website, and other relevant statistics. The amount of information sent depends on the settings on your web browser; please refer to your browser to learn the information that it sends.

All such information will be used only to assist us in providing effective services on this website. We may from time to time supply owners or operators of third party websites from which it is possible to link to our website the information relating to the number of users linking to our website from such third party website. You cannot be identified from this information.

We use the information we automatically receive from your web browser to see which pages you visit within our website, which website you visited before coming to ours, and where you go after you leave. We can then develop statistics that are helpful to understand how our visitors use this website. We use this information in the aggregate to measure the use of our website and to administer and improve our website. This statistical data is interpreted by in its continuing effort to present the website content that visitors are seeking in a format they find most helpful.

COOKIES

In common with many other website operators, we may use standard technology called 'cookies' on this site. Cookies are small text files stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive and are used for record keeping purposes.

Use of cookies makes web surfing easier by performing certain functions such as saving your personal preferences regarding your use of the particular web site and ensuring that you do not need to re-enter your details each time you visit our site. Our cookies enable us to understand who has seen which pages and advertisements, to determine how frequently particular pages are visited and to determine the most popular areas of our website.

We use cookies to enrich your experience of using this website by providing you with focused information each time you visit our website based on our learnings of your preferences during your visits to the site.

You can usually change your browser settings to prevent cookies being stored and to erase any cookies which have been stored. Please note, if you do turn cookies off it will limit the service that we are able to provide to you and may affect your visitor experience.

SECURITY OF INFORMATION

We take the security of your information seriously. We have implemented required technologies and policies, with the objective of protecting your privacy from unauthorised access and improper use, and periodically review the same.

MONITORING

We may monitor or record telephone calls made by you to our customer care/help desk for security purposes and to improve the quality of services that we provide to you.

REVISION TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We aim to meet high standards and our policies and procedures are, therefore, constantly under review. We may, from time to time, change our security and privacy policies. Accordingly, we recommend that you check this page periodically in order to review our current policies, as your use of our services provides your acceptance to the privacy policy prevailing at the time of use of our services.

THIRD PARTIES

This page contains hyperlinks to other websites which are provided for your convenience. In addition, you may have linked to our website from another website. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other websites, even if the access to those websites is by use of links from our website.

We make no promises or guarantees regarding data collection on the hyper-linked pages and on websites that are not owned by us. We recommend that you check the policy of each website you visit, or link from, and contact the owners or operators of such websites if you have any concerns or questions.

ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION

You can (subject to payment of an appropriate fee) request a copy of the personal information held about you by us at any time by contacting us.

UPDATING AND CORRECTING INFORMATION

We aim to keep our information about you as accurate as possible. If you would like to review or change the details you have supplied us with, you may do so by contacting us or by changing your profile on our website. Please include your name, address and/or email address when you contact us as this helpus to ensure that we accept amendments only from the correct person. We encourage you to promptly update your personal information if it changes.

CONTACT US

We welcome your views about our website and our privacy policy. Please feel free to contact us if you have any queries or comments.

The information used in the website have been purchased from a Third party vendor. We are not responsible for any incorrect information.

Any phone number registered with us will be used for promotional activity.
